minijobz.com 2014-12-09

# minijobz-Get your mini jobs done at low cost, Earn money advertising your services, Get paid to click...

Privacy Policy

Welcome to the Minijobz, a web service utility that connects employers and workers on a micro level. The Minijobz is operated by Minijobz, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates ("us," "we",  "Minijobz", "site" or "Minijobz"). By using or accessing the Minijobz, you agree that you have read, understand and are bound by these Terms of Use ("Terms"). We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change or delete portions of these Terms at any time without further notice. Your continued use of the Minijobz after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms.

Minijobz Principles

We built Our website to make it easy to (a) advertise your product (b) find people who will be interested in helping you promote your website, product, etc. (c) find people who will help you do work for you - finish tasks you usually are not able to finish yourself or you want more people to work on a task (d) convert your work into earnings. We understand you may not want everyone in the world to access your personal information; that is why all personal information is hidden from other users. Our  privacy settings is very strict and does not allow other users to see any of your personal information except your member ID $ Name.

Minijobz does not share information with other users. As employer you choose what information you put in response to replying to a worker. As a worker you choose what information you put in response to replying to an employer. We suggest you not to reply with any personal information such as your MSN ID, Skype ID, Email, phone number, etc.. There is no need to publish any of your personal information as all communication in Minijobz system is based upon user ID.

If you are trying to submit finished task and campaign (job) is asking you to (requires you to)  enter personal information, credit card information or any other information about you, such campaign violates xxxxxxxx principles and you should not continue. We suggest you not to continue with that campaign and immediately report this violation to us. Use Contact us form or Plain Job's email and report campaign/job ID and disclose as many details as possible. We will make sure to immediately terminate campaigns that violates our rules.

Safe Use of xxxxxxxx

In general xxxxxxxx is suitable for everyone but certain jobs might not be acceptable for some people. If you are a child, below 21 years old or feel offended by adult material, please do not accept a job that might be offensive to you. You should not accept any job that feels offensive or disturbing to you. Every job details should describe what is it about. If you think the job might be offensive, do not continue and do not accept that job. There are plenty of other jobs to select from.

The Information We Collect

When you visit xxxxxxxx you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register with xxxxxxxx, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address  and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter xxxxxxxx, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all xxxxxxxx visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login information so you don't have to login again when you come back to xxxxxxxx. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. If you don't want other people who use same computer to login to your xxxxxxxx account then you should always log out of your account after finishing with your activities.

You post new campaigns or submit finished tasks on the Site at your own risk. Although you should never disclose your personal information to other users you communicate with, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that information you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal or termination of your account, copies of User Content and your previous actions may remain view-able in cached and archived pages.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on xxxxxxxx is a violation of the xxxxxxxx Terms of Service and should be reported to us using xxxxxxxx' email published on the Site.

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email or instant message in your name inviting him or her to visit the site, and may send up to two reminders to them. xxxxxxxx stores this information to send invitations and reminders, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, to allow you to see invitations you have sent, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us through the Contact us form on our Contact us or to xxxxxxxx' email published on the Site to request that we remove this information from our database.

xxxxxxxx may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, etc. in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.

By using xxxxxxxx, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and EU countries.

Children Under Age 13

xxxxxxxx does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for xxxxxxxx or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on xxxxxxxx. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us through the Contact us form or via xxxxxxxx' email which are both available on the Site.

Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18

We recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

Use of Information Obtained by xxxxxxxx

When you register with xxxxxxxx, you create your own account. Your profile information and email  are not displayed to other users. Unless you decide to share your personal information with other users, the only information displayed is your account ID. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by xxxxxxxx that we think you may find valuable.

We will also use your mailing address information to send you a PIN code you need to activate payments to you. In case you select check as payment option we will send a check payment to you directly.

xxxxxxxx may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if another users sends you a message regarding a job or a task, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.

Generally, you may opt out of such emails by changing notification settings under "My Account" tab, though xxxxxxxx reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, xxxxxxxx Platform developers and other users of xxxxxxxx, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile.

Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

xxxxxxxx will not share information in your profile with third parties.

Users data

When you use xxxxxxxx certain information you post or share with other users, such as personal information, campaign data, task data, comments, messages, photos, videos or other information, may be shared with other users. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that when posting any information about a) campaigns or b) tasks to xxxxxxxx this information may become publicly available.

Links

xxxxxxxx may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site or to visit any website they find on xxxxxxxx to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by xxxxxxxx.

Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on xxxxxxxx are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. xxxxxxxx does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on xxxxxxxx unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by xxxxxxxx and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

Changing or Removing Information

xxxxxxxx users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by sending an email to xxxxxxxx and request such action to be taken. Information will be updated if xxxxxxxx staff determines user did a mistake when submitting personal information, mail address, email or any other information submitted. Individuals who wish to deactivate their xxxxxxxx account may do so by contraction us and request account termination. We will terminate the account. Once account is terminated user will not be able to login and perform any actions otherwise available in xxxxxxxx system. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to other members of xxxxxxxx.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on xxxxxxxx, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another xxxxxxxx user) or information that was shared by starting a campaign, submitting or rating a task you generally cannot remove such information.

Security

All data entered by our users (except some payment information) is saved on xxxxxxxx servers. Servers are based in United States operated by a hosting company. Hosting company should is responsible to update the server(s) with latest patches and prevent any possible attacks and prevent other people than those authorized by xxxxxxxx staff from accessing xxxxxxxx database.

xxxxxxxx takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), that information is always entered and processed at online payment system services such as Paypal or 2Checkout or others that are  used to perform transactions. Before initiating payment to xxxxxxxx make sure to read Terms and Privacy policy at Paypal.com

Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of xxxxxxxx Web Site, please contact us through the Contact us form or via xxxxxxxx email published on the Site.

Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of xxxxxxxx, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy,   
please contact us through the Contact us form or via xxxxxxxx email published on the Site.

Thank you  
MiniJob PHP 2.1b  
Job Script
